

Tentang Saya

Saya lulusan teknik komputer jaringan dari SMK Negeri Situraja. Memiliki kemampuan dalam menganalisa, pemecahan masalah, critical thinking. Selalu menggunakan data untuk mengambil keputusan. Mencari kesempatan untuk mengembangkan bakat dan kemampuan saya. Saya juga ahli dalam bidang editing video maupun foto. Menggunakan microsoft office, bekerja sama dengan tim dan juga dapat mengerjakan pekerjaan dengan tepat waktu

Kemampuan

- Editing Video
- Canva
- Data Entry
- Microsoft Office
- E-commerce Management

Kontak

- +62 819 4958 5560
- Siscafp987@gmail.com
- Dusun Kucing RT 04/04,
 Desa Linggajaya, Kecamatan
 Cisitu, Sumedang, 45363

Sisca Febrian Pratami

Pendidikan

- 2019- 2022SMK Negeri SiturajaTeknik Komputer Jaringan
- 2022 Sekarang
 Universitas Pendidikan
 Indonesia
 Teknik Komputer

Pengalaman Kerja

Admin Tokopedia/Shopee/Itemku

Januari 2021 - Mei 2022

- Melayani Konsumen dengan ramah
- Memberikan informasi terkait produk yang dibahas
- Memeriksa persediaan barang
- Teknisi Komputer di UPI KampusUPI Sumedang

Maret 2021 - April 2021

- Menginstall OS windows pada komputer
- Memasang kabel jaringan pada server
- Memonitoring beberapa software komputer
- Pelatihan di PT. Satu VisitIndocreative

Mei 2021

 Instalasi dan konfigurasi jaringan pada komputer



Biography

I graduated from Situraja State Vocational School with a degree in computer network engineering. My expertise includes analysis, problem-solving, and critical thinking. I base my decisions on data and continuously strive to improve my skills and abilities. Furthermore, I have a specialization in video and photo editing, excel in using Microsoft Office, work effectively in teams, and am dedicated to meeting deadlines.

Skill

- Video Production
- Canva
- Data Entry
- Microsoft Office software
- E-commerce Management

Contact me

- +62 819 4958 5560
- Siscafp987@gmail.com
- Kucing Hill RT 04/04, Linggajaya Village, Cisitu District, Sumedang, 45363

Sisca Febrian Pratami

Education

- 2019- 2022
 Computer Network Engineering program at Situraja State High School
- 2022 PresentUniversity of EducationComputer Engineering

Work Experience

E-commerce

January 2021 - May 2022

- Help customers politely.
- Provide information about the products that were discussed.
- Inventory verification
- Computer Technician at Universityof Education Sumedang Campus

March 2021 - April 2021

- Set up the Windows operating system on the computer.
- Installation of network cables on the server
- PT. One Visit Indocreative TrainingMay 2021
 - Setting up and configuring computer networks